Joseph Christian

Business Information System Graduate | Full-Stack Developer

Balikpapan, Indonesia | +62895361700188 | josephjcwork@gmail.com, LinkedIn, Github

SUMMARY

I am a Web Developer specializing in creating responsive, user-focused websites. My work is driven by a commitment to delivering efficient, scalable, and accessible solutions that enhance user experiences while meeting business goals. With a strong attention to detail and problem-solving mindset, I strive to ensure every project exceeds expectations and delivers real value.

EXPERIENCE

PT Cross Network Indonesia

Surabaya

Front-End Web Developer Internship

July, 2023 – December, 2023

- Implemented intuitive UI designs for websites using Tailwind CSS, ensuring responsive and user-friendly interfaces.
- Develop functional websites with HTML and Javascript in collaboration with fellow programmers to provide a seamless user experience.

Petra Christian University

Surabaya

Full Stack Developer (Freelance)

February, 2024 – June 2024

- Developed a website using Laravel to streamline helpdesk services for the ELTC unit at Petra Christian University.
- Conducted requirements analysis, designed databases, and implemented ticketing system features for related services.
- Collaborated with the PPSI and ELTC units at Petra Christian University to ensure successful testing and implementation of the system.

PROJECT

Personal Website

November, 2024 – November, 2024

This platform highlights my skills and my projects. Built with React and TypeScript, the website utilizes Tailwind CSS to deliver a seamless and responsive user experience.

Public Forum Discussion

October, 2024 - October, 2024

This project was created during my React course on Dicoding to put my skills into practice. It's a public forum where users can join discussions and explore threads. This project was built with React, Redux, and other React ecosystems..

Helpdesk for Services at ELTC Unit of Petra Christian University

February, 2024 – June, 2024

This platform is designed to facilitate the management of complaints, classroom bookings, and other services for the Excellence in Learning and Teaching Center unit at Petra Christian University. Each service operates through a ticketing system, ensuring more structured and efficient management, and it's developed with Laravel, PHP, and JavaScript, blending Bootstrap and CSS to create a seamless and dynamic user experience.

EDUCATION

Petra Christian University

Surabaya

Business Information System, GPA: 3.62/4.00

August, 2020 – July, 2024

• Thesis: Helpdesk Information System for Services At Excellence in Learning and Teaching Center To Increase User Satisfaction

CORE SKILL

- Programing Language: Javascript, React, Typescript, PHP, Python
- Framework: Laravel
- **Database:** PostgreSQL & MySQL
- Soft Skill: Teamwork, Problem Solving, Adaptability

CERTIFICATION

- Learn to Create a Website with React by Dicoding
- Learn Web Application Fundamentals with React by <u>Dicoding</u>
 Become a React Web Developer Expert by <u>Dicoding</u>